Life's harsh. Why behave?
Truth or Consequences, N.M. is a action, crime, drama
film directed by Kiefer Sutherland.
Raymond Lembecke is a con just out of prison after serving time
for selling drugs for his mob boss Tony Vago.
(Lembecke was innocent and took the rap for Vago.) Lembecke thinks Vago owes him big time so, when his former boss gets him a
measly job in a warehouse, he decides on revenge and plans to steal a million dollars worth of drugs from him.
Raymond Lembecke, played by Vincent Gallo.
Curtis Freley, played by Kiefer Sutherland.
Wayne, played by Max Perlich.
Tony Vago, played by Rod Steiger.
Eddie Grillo, played by John C. McGinley.
Sir, played by Martin Sheen.
Truth or Consequences, N.M.
is a 1997 American neo-noir film directed by Kiefer Sutherland starring Sutherland, Vincent Gallo,
Mykelti Williamson, Kevin Pollak, Max Perlich, Rod Steiger, and Kim Dickens, among others.
The film explores themes of prison, robbery, hostage, new mexico, racism.
The tone is emotional.